Guide to the Barbara Shailor, Deputy Provost for the Arts, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Barbara Shailor, deputy provost for the arts, Yale University, records
1979-2010
RU 1087
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
20.25
(22 boxes)
The records consist of correspondence, reports, committee files, meeting minutes, and subject files maintained by Barbara Shailor as deputy provost for the arts.
Yale University. Office of the Provost
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 3-B (YRG 3-B), Records of Yale deputy, associate, and assistant provosts.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The records were transferred from the Office of the Provost, 2008 and 2014.
Conditions Governing Access
The collection is restricted for thirty-five years from end of tenure of provost Shailor. It will be available for research in 2047.
Biographical / Historical
The Office of the Provost was created by vote of the Yale Corporation in 1919. The establishment of the office was part of a general University reorganization plan that was submitted to the Corporation by the Committee on Educational Policy. By the term of Provost Edgar S. Furniss (1937-1958), the office had evolved to essentially its present-day function. The provost is the chief academic officer of the University, responsible for administering all of the internal operations of the University concerned with education and research.
Biographical / Historical
Barbara A. Shailor was appointed deputy provost for the arts in July 2003. As such, she is involved in shaping and implementing the academic, administrative, strategic planning, and budgetary policies of the Schools of Art, Architecture, Drama, Music, and Divinity; the Institute of Sacred Music; the Classics, Music and Religious Studies departments; the Yale University Art Gallery, the Yale Center for British Art, the Paul Mellon Center in London, the Digital Media Center for the Arts; and the University Library system.
Ms. Shailor came to Yale in 2001 as the director of the Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library. Prior to that, she served as dean of Douglass College, professor of classics at Rutgers University, and a faculty member and administrator at Bucknell University. Her field of specialization is Latin paleography and codicology, encompassing the study of Visigothic manuscripts copied and illuminated in northern Spain in the 10th and 11th centuries.
Ms. Shailor has published extensively, including five books and a series of articles on medieval and renaissance manuscripts. She has been awarded grants from the National Endowment for the Humanities, the American Council of Learned Societies, and the American Philosophical Society. She is currently serving as treasurer of the Medieval Academy of America and as a trustee of the Samuel H. Kress Foundation, as well as on the boards of the Public Leadership Education Network in Washington D.C. and the Center for Parliamentary History at Yale. Dr. Shailor was elected to membership in the Comité international de paléographie latine in Paris and the Grolier Club of New York City in 2000.
Barbara Shailor received an undergraduate degree magna cum laude from Wilson College and a Ph.D. in Classical Philology from the University of Cincinnati.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of correspondence, reports, committee files, meeting minutes, and subject files maintained by Barbara Shailor as deputy provost for the arts.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Universities and colleges -- Administration; Shailor, Barbara A., 1948-; Yale University -- Administration; Yale University. Office of the Provost
- Barbara Shailor, deputy provost for the arts, records, 1989-2006; Accession 2009-A-120; 16
  - School of Drama
    - 2004-2005
      - Director of Development, Mark Hough, 2004-2005, 2003 May 28 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - Budget Meeting, 2004-2005 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - Yale Rep, 2004-2005 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - Development Shubert FDN 2004-2005, 2004 November 30 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - Professor Adjunct of Playwriting, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence
      - Budget Meeting, 2003 October 27 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      - Budget Meetings, 2004 March 5 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - Yale Rep School - Staffing Issues, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - Auditing, 2003 September 29 (Box 1, Folder 9)
      - Acting Chair Search, 2002 2003 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      - Faculty Appointments 2003-2004, 2003 August 13 (Box 1, Folder 11)
      - Reappointment Process, 2003 January 11 (Box 1, Folder 12)
      - Strategic Plan, 2003-2004 (Box 1, Folder 13)
      - 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 14)
      - 5-Year Plan, 2002 September 19 (Box 1, Folder 15)
      - 5-Year Plan, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 16)
      - Salaries, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Report from Dean to EPC (Draft), 2004 January 7 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Stage Management Search, 2004 June 6 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - EFA - Proposal, 2003 November 20 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Editor Theater Magazine Assistant Professor Adjunct Search, 2003 February 13 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - 2003 Promotions, 2002 November 12 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Faculty Appointments and Promotions
      - Appointments, 2002- 2003 (Box 1, Folder 25)
      - Appointments/Promotions, 2001- 2002 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Budries and Munk, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Dramaturgy Students, 2000-2002 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Marketing Director, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - 2001-2002
      - Tuition/Financial Aid 2003, 2001 November 28 (Box 1, Folder 31)
      - Storage, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 32)
      - Appointments Procedure, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 33)
      - Marketing Faculty Position, 1999 June 2 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - 2000-2001
      - 5 Year Retrospective Budget, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 36)
      - Drama/GESO, 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 37)
      - Salaries, 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 38)
      - 149 York St., 1995-2002 (Box 1, Folder 40)
      - Correspondence, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - School of Music
    - 2004-2005
      - Leaves of Absence, 2004 September 1 (Box 1, Folder 43)
      - Annual Chair Meeting, 2004 September - October (Box 1, Folder 44)
      - Faculty Forms, 2004 March - November (Box 1, Folder 45)
      - Department Salaries 2004-2005, 2004 March - June (Box 1, Folder 46)
      - Department Leaves 2004-2005, 2004 February 12 (Box 1, Folder 47)
      - Humanities Advisory Committee Minutes, 2004 May 19 (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - 2003-2004
      - Chair Meeting, 2003 August - December (Box 1, Folder 49)
      - 1998-2003 (Box 1, Folder 50)
      - Music, 2003 May 19 (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - 2001-2003 (Box 1, Folder 53)
      - Senior Search, 2000-2003 (Box 1, Folder 54)
      - Plantinga Retirement, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 55)
      - Senior Search: HARRISON, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 56)
      - KOFI, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Religious Studies
    - Annual Chair Meeting, 2004 November 10 (Box 1, Folder 58)
    - 2003-2004 (Box 1, Folder 59)
    - 2001-2002 / 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 60)
    - GRECO Roman Luncheons, 2003 September 23 (Box 1, Folder 62)
    - Junior Searches, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 63)
    - Senior Search, 1999-2002 (Box 1, Folder 64)
    - WEAVER, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 67)
    - WEIS Professorships, 2003-2004 (Box 1, Folder 69)
    - New Testament Colloquy, 1999-2001 (Box 1, Folder 70)
    - Religious Studies, 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - British Art Center (BAC)
    - General, 2002 January 23 (Box 1, Folder 72)
    - Board Meeting, 2002 May 6 (Box 1, Folder 73)
    - Advisory Board, 2001 October 1 (Box 1, Folder 74)
    - Mellon Executors, 2001-2003 (Box 1, Folder 75)
    - Annual Report - First Draft, 2001 January 14 (Box 1, Folder 76)
    - 2000-2001
      - Budget, 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 77)
      - Staff Positions/Promotions, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 78)
      - Advisory, 2000 November 3 (Box 1, Folder 79)
      - Annual Report, 1999- 2000 (Box 1, Folder 80)
      - Advisory Committee, 2001 May 7 (Box 1, Folder 81)
      - Transition, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 82)
    - Mellon Grant, 2004- 2005 (Box 2, Folder 84)
    - BAC, 2003- 2004 (Box 2, Folder 85)
    - 2002-2003
      - Advisory Board, 2003- 2004 (Box 2, Folder 86)
      - Advisory Board, 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 87)
      - Annual Report, 2001- 2002 (Box 2, Folder 88)
      - Correspondence, 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 90)
      - Salaries 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 91)
      - 2002 Financial Report, 2003 January 7 (Box 2, Folder 92)
      - OUTREACH (also in Gallery file), 2003 January 30 (Box 2, Folder 93)
      - Curators as Instructors, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 94)
      - Long-Range Plan, 2002- 2003 (Box 2, Folder 95)
  - Lewis Walpole Library, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 96)
  - Yale University Art Gallery (YUAG)
    - Art Gallery Budgets (Meeting), 2004-2005 (Box 2, Folder 97)
    - Board Meeting, 2004 October (Box 2, Folder 98)
    - Board Meeting, 2004 April 20
      - Auditing 2003-2004, 2003 September 29 (Box 2, Folder 99)
      - Board Meeting Agenda, 2004 April 22 (Box 2, Folder 100)
    - 2003-2004
      - Expendable Gifts, 2003 August 22 (Box 2, Folder 101)
      - Renovation Phase 1, 2003-2004 (Box 2, Folder 102)
    - 2002-2003
      - Leaves for Curators ART GALLERY, 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 104)
      - Salaries, 2002 May 30 (Box 2, Folder 106)
      - Plagiarism, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 107)
      - General Correspondence, 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 108)
      - Outreach (also in BAC file), 2003 January 30 (Box 2, Folder 109)
      - Graduate Research Assistantship, 2003 May 1 (Box 2, Folder 110)
      - GA Issues 5 year plan, 2001 June 26 (Box 2, Folder 112)
    - Correspondence, 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 113)
    - Arts Area Presentation, 2002 March 27 (Box 2, Folder 114)
    - Art Gallery Budget and Staff Projection, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 115)
    - 2001-2002
      - Phasing Study, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 116)
      - 5-Year Plan, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 117)
      - Conservation Center, 2001 November 8 (Box 2, Folder 119)
      - Project Cost 2001-2002, 2001 November 5 (Box 2, Folder 120)
      - Board Meeting Nov. 2001, 2001 November 14 (Box 2, Folder 121)
      - Site 2 Art Gallery, 1999-2002 (Box 2, Folder 122)
    - 2000-2001
      - Financial Planning, 1999-2001 (Box 2, Folder 123)
      - Correspondence, 2000 November 10 (Box 2, Folder 124)
      - Design Process, 2000- 2001 (Box 2, Folder 125)
    - 1999-2000
      - Architect Selection, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 127)
      - Correspondence, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 128)
      - positions, 2000 June 7 (Box 2, Folder 129)
      - Kahn Renovation, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 130)
    - 1998-1999
      - Correspondence, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 131)
  - Classics
    - Senior Search - HANOOSH, M, 2001 May 1 (Box 2, Folder 132)
    - Senior Search: JANKO, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 134)
    - 1998-1999/1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 137)
    - 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 138)
    - Searches
      - Junior Searches, 2003 June 23 (Box 2, Folder 139)
      - Senior Searches, 1997- 2002 (Box 2, Folder 140)
    - 2001-2002/2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 141)
    - 2004-2005
      - Salaries 2004-2005, 2004 June 4 (Box 2, Folder 143)
      - Correspondence, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 144)
      - Senior Latinist Search, 2002-2004 (Box 2, Folder 145)
      - Faculty Appointment Forms, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 146)
      - Leaves of Absence, 2003-2004 (Box 2, Folder 148)
      - Classics Chair Meeting 2004-2005 (Box 2, Folder 149)
    - 2003-2004
      - Salaries, 2003-2004 (Box 2, Folder 151)
      - Correspondence, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 153)
    - Latin Search, 1998-2002 (Box 2, Folder 156)
  - OT/NT - Collins
    - Correspondence, 1999- 2002 (Box 3, Folder 173)
  - Divinity School
    - Correspondence 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 177)
    - Self Support, 2001-2002 (Box 3, Folder 178)
    - Long Range Plan, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 179)
    - Assessments, 2002 July 17 (Box 3, Folder 180)
    - ATS Visit Feb 17-19, 2003, 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 181)
    - Gray Chair, 2001-2002 (Box 3, Folder 182)
    - Organizational Review Divinity, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 183)
    - Weinstein Buddhism Position, 2001 November 9 (Box 3, Folder 184)
    - Tuition and Financial Aid 2003, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 185)
    - Mar Judaic Studies, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 189)
    - 7.7 Million Gift, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 192)
    - Development
      - Brochure, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 194)
      - General, 1997- 2003 (Box 3, Folder 195)
      - Carnegie, 2001 December 5 (Box 3, Folder 196)
      - Minus Chair, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 198)
      - Luce Grants, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 202)
      - Center for World Christianity, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 203)
      - P.R., Development Search, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 205)
    - Pastoral Excellence (M. Volf), 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 208)
    - Center for Faith and Culture (Volf), 2003 February 12 (Box 3, Folder 209)
    - Volf-Lilly Grant, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 210)
    - Lilly Grants - Divinity, 1999-2003 (Box 3, Folder 211)
    - Carpenter - Divinity, 2001-2004 (Box 3, Folder 212)
  - School of Music
    - Faculty
      - Correspondence, 1999-2000 (Box 4, Folder 213)
      - Deanship Search Copy of President's File, 1994- 1995 (Box 4, Folder 215)
    - Hendrie Hall, 1999 May 24 (Box 4, Folder 216)
    - Woolsey Hall Renovation, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 217)
    - Stoeckel, 1998-2000 (Box 4, Folder 218)
    - Woolsey Hall Project, 1995-1998 (Box 4, Folder 219)
    - Music Accreditation, 1987- 1999 (Box 4, Folder 220)
    - 1999-2000
      - Graduate Students, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 221)
      - Oboes, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 222)
      - Staff Reorganization, 2000 April (Box 4, Folder 223)
    - 2000-2001
      - Brochure, 2000-2001 (Box 4, Folder 224)
      - 5 Year Financial Plan, 2000 August 18 (Box 4, Folder 225)
      - Wilson, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 226)
    - 2001-2002
      - FAC Salaries, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 227)
      - Correspondence, 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 228)
      - FAC Plan, 2001 April 23 (Box 4, Folder 229)
      - Computers, 2001 November 26 (Box 4, Folder 230)
      - Reorganization: School of Music Meeting, 2002 April 9 (Box 4, Folder 231)
      - Voice and Music History Positions, 2002 March 6 (Box 4, Folder 232)
      - Correspondence, 2000-2001 (Box 4, Folder 234)
    - 2002-2003
      - Music School/Norfolk Salaries 2002-2003 (Box 4, Folder 235)
      - Reappointments 2003-2004, 1998-2003 (Box 4, Folder 236)
      - Correspondence 2002-2003 (Box 4, Folder 237)
      - Appointments 2002-2003, 1998-2003 (Box 4, Folder 240)
    - 2003-2004
      - Music School, 2002-2004 (Box 4, Folder 242)
      - Leaves 2003-2004/2004-2005, 1998-2003 (Box 4, Folder 243)
      - Professor of Composition Search, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 245)
      - Budget Meeting, 2004 September 8 (Box 4, Folder 246)
  - School of Art
    - Development
      - Adobe Systems, 1999 March 6 (Box 4, Folder 247)
      - Miscellaneous Correspondence/General, 1998-2003 (Box 4, Folder 249)
    - Faculty Matters
      - Computer Position Art Faculty, 1998 December 7 (Box 4, Folder 255)
      - Correspondence/Misc., 1998-1999 (Box 4, Folder 257)
    - Junior Sculpture, 2000-2001 (Box 4, Folder 258)
    - Appointment Procedure for Adjunct Faculty, 1988-1999 (Box 4, Folder 259)
    - Search Questionnares, 1999-2000 (Box 4, Folder 260)
    - Shoreline Alliance, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 261)
    - 1999-2000
      - Budgets, 1998-1999 (Box 4, Folder 262)
      - Dean's Letters, 2000 March 26 (Box 4, Folder 263)
      - Faculty Matters, 1999-2000 (Box 4, Folder 264)
    - 2000-2001
      - China Program, 1999 September - November (Box 4, Folder 265)
      - Budget 2000, 1999- 2000 (Box 4, Folder 266)
      - Financial Aid, 2000 September (Box 4, Folder 267)
    - 2001-2002 (Box 4)
      - Dean's Letter Summer 2001, 2001 June 1 (Box 4, Folder 268)
      - Appointments, 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 269)
  - Divinity School
    - 2004-2005
      - Budget Meeting, 2004 December 3 (Box 4, Folder 272)
      - I and A, 2004 July 15 (Box 4, Folder 273)
      - General Correspondence, 2001 May 14 (Box 4, Folder 274)
      - Trip to NYC, 2003 August 2 (Box 4, Folder 275)
      - Endowments, 2003- 2005 (Box 4, Folder 276)
    - 2003-2004
      - Faculty Appointments, 2003-2004 (Box 4, Folder 277)
      - Budgets, 2003 October 6 (Box 4, Folder 278)
      - Annual Report 2002-2003, 2003 July 17 (Box 4, Folder 279)
      - Audit, 2004 January - March (Box 4, Folder 280)
      - Miscellaneous, 2004 May 10 (Box 4, Folder 281)
    - Miscellaneous (Contact list), 2003 (Box 4, Folder 282)
  - Institute of Sacred Music (ISM)
    - Visitors
      - New Candidates, 2004-2005 (Box 4, Folder 283)
      - Candidates
    - Overviews, 2003- 2004 (Box 5, Folder 334)
  - School of Art
    - 1995-1996
      - Budget, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 335)
      - Fosburgh - Art Gallery, 1995 November 17 (Box 5, Folder 336)
      - Dean Search, 1990-1996 (Box 5, Folder 337)
    - Buildings/Facilities
      - Art/Drama Maintenance, 1999-2000 (Box 5, Folder 338)
      - Holcombe T. Green Hall, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 339)
      - Hammond Hall, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 340)
      - Sprinkler - Rudolph Bldg, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 341)
      - Darkrooms, 1982-1987 (Box 5, Folder 342)
  - Liturgic Search - senior, 2000-2001 (Box 5, Folder 343)
  - ISM - Litugic Search (1 of 2), 1997-2001 (Box 5, Folder 344)
  - ISM Faculty
    - Art and Architecture Search (1996-1997 ISM), 1997- 1998 (Box 5, Folder 345)
  - School of Music - Glee Club
    - Lockwood, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 348)
    - ISM Liturgical Junior Search, 1999-2000 (Box 5, Folder 349)
    - Glee Club, 1991-1993 (Box 5, Folder 351)
  - Art Gallery
    - Endowments, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 352)
    - Steering Committee, 1997- 2007 (Box 6, Folder 353 - 356)
  - McNeil
    - 1999 (Box 6, Folder 357)
    - Correspondence, 1994-1996 (Box 6, Folder 358)
    - 1995-1996 (Box 6, Folder 359)
    - 1997 (Box 6, Folder 360 - 361)
  - Divinity School Dean Search Committee Folder, 2000 August 16 (Box 6, Folder 362)
  - Public Art
    - Public Art Committee, 2005 October 20 (Box 6, Folder 363)
    - Outdoor Sculpture Committee, 2003-2005 (Box 6, Folder 364)
    - 1993- 2004 (Box 6, Folder 365)
  - Imaging America, 1999-2001 (Box 6, Folder 366)
  - ArtSTOR, 2001 August 29 (Box 6, Folder 367)
  - Luna Imaging, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 368)
  - Barbara - Discretionary, 2004-2005 (Box 6, Folder 369)
  - Campaign - LIBRARY, 2004 October 6 (Box 6, Folder 370)
  - Capital Campaign
    - Information Technology, 2004-2005 (Box 6, Folder 371)
    - Divinity, 2004- 2006 (Box 6, Folder 372)
    - Library, 2003-2004 (Box 6, Folder 373)
    - Architecture, 2004 October - December (Box 6, Folder 374)
    - Drama School, 2004 June - October (Box 6, Folder 375)
    - School of Music, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 376)
    - Collection of Musical Instruments, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 377)
    - Art Gallery, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 378)
  - PONPO
    - 2000-2002 (Box 7, Folder 381 - 382)
    - Grant Reports, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 384)
  - Diana's discretionary, 2000-2002 (Box 7, Folder 385 - 386)
  - Digital Database (Danuta), 2002 September 19 (Box 7, Folder 388)
  - Marie Curie Symposium (Nov 6-8, 2003), 2003-2004 (Box 7, Folder 392)
  - Reciepts - Manana, 2003-2004 (Box 7, Folder 393)
  - Collection of Musical Instruments
    - 2004-2005 (Box 7, Folder 395)
    - Advisory Board, 2003-2005 (Box 7, Folder 396)
    - Correspondence, 2004 May - June (Box 7, Folder 397)
    - Instrument/Deposit, 1968- 2004 (Box 7, Folder 398)
    - Possible Candidates, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 399)
  - Norfolk
    - 2004-2005
      - Chamber Music Festival, 2005 June 24 (Box 7, Folder 400)
      - Meeting 8/12/2004, 2004-2005 (Box 7, Folder 401 - 402)
      - Evening, 2003 August 15 (Box 7, Folder 403)
    - 2003-2004
      - General, 2003-2004 (Box 7, Folder 404)
      - Meeting, 2004 January 21 (Box 7, Folder 405)
      - Annual Report, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 406)
      - Housing Survey and Housing, 1998-2000 (Box 7, Folder 407)
    - 2002-2003
      - Housing, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 408)
      - 2002 (Box 7, Folder 409)
      - Day, 2002 July 13 (Box 7, Folder 410)
      - Music - Summer 2004, 2003-2004 (Box 7, Folder 411)
      - 2002-2003 (Box 7, Folder 412)
    - Battel-Stoeckel, 1974-2002 (Box 7, Folder 414)
    - 1999-2000
      - Reports, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 415)
      - Correspondence, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 416)
  - University Council - Music, 1997- 1999 (Box 8, Folder 417)
  - Yale Corporation/Committees [restricted 50 years from date of creation]
    - EPC, 2005 December 9 (Box 8, Folder 418)
    - Building and Grounds Committee, 2006 April 21 (Box 8, Folder 419)
    - Corporation, 2005 January - February (Box 8, Folder 420)
    - Architecture EPC, 2001 May - November (Box 8, Folder 421)
    - Divinity Corporation Material, 2002-2003 (Box 8, Folder 422)
    - Corporation Material, 2003 January - February (Box 8, Folder 423)
    - EPC Feb. 8 2002, 1999-2001 (Box 8, Folder 424)
    - Yale Corporation - Distance Learning, 1999-2000 (Box 8, Folder 425)
    - Corporation EPC Music at Yale, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 427)
    - Corporation Retreat at Stamford, 1999 July 21 (Box 8, Folder 428)
    - Corporation, 2003-2004 (Box 8, Folder 429)
    - University Council - School of Architecture, 2001 January - June (Box 8, Folder 430 - 431)
    - UCC - Architecture, 1999-2001 (Box 8, Folder 432)
  - Institute of Sacred Music (ISM)
    - 2003-2004
      - Barbara and Margot, 2003-2004 (Box 8, Folder 434)
      - ISM Miscellaneous Correspondence, 2003-2004 (Box 8, Folder 435)
      - ISM Administrative Organizational Flow Chart, 2004 June 7 (Box 8, Folder 436)
    - 2002-2003
      - Music History Junior Search, 2002-2003 (Box 8, Folder 437)
      - Junior Liturgy Search, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 438)
      - Visiting Faculty, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 439)
      - Salaries, 2002 July 11 (Box 8, Folder 440)
      - ISM Meeting with Alison, 2002-2003 (Box 8, Folder 442)
      - ISM General Correspondence, 2002-2003 (Box 8, Folder 443)
      - Visiting Faculty 2003, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 444)
    - Music History Search, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 445)
    - Liturgical Studies Chapel, 2001-2004 (Box 8, Folder 447)
    - SAAC ISM, 2002 December 17 (Box 8, Folder 449)
    - Issues, 1999-2002 (Box 8, Folder 451)
    - Faculty Salaries, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 452)
    - Correspondence, 2000- 2002 (Box 8, Folder 453)
    - 2001-2002
      - Business Manager, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 454)
      - Choir, 2001 September 9 (Box 9, Folder 455)
      - French Memorial, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 456)
      - Moeller Organ, 2001- 2002 (Box 9, Folder 459)
      - Ortel Organ, 2001-2002 (Box 9, Folder 460)
      - London Tour, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 461)
      - Annual Report (2001-2002) (1999-2000), 2001 January 9 (Box 9, Folder 462)
      - Board, 2001 October 17 (Box 9, Folder 463)
      - Correspondence, 2000- 2001 (Box 9, Folder 464)
    - Hawkin's Replacement - Religion and Literature, 1999- 2002 (Box 9, Folder 465)
    - 5-Year Draft, 2000-2001 (Box 9, Folder 466)
    - 5-Year Plan
      - Approvals for 2002-2003, 2002 August - October (Box 9, Folder 467)
      - 5-Year Plan, 2001-2003 (Box 9, Folder 468 - 470)
    - 2000-2001
      - Advisory Committee, 1999-2001 (Box 9, Folder 473)
      - Development, 2001-2002 (Box 9, Folder 474)
      - Faculty Salaries 2000-2001, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 475)
    - 1999-2000
      - Ad Hoc, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 477)
      - Faculty Appointments/Promotions, 2001-2002 (Box 9, Folder 478)
      - Correspondence, 1997-1999 (Box 9, Folder 479)
      - Correspondence, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 480)
      - Curriculum Committee, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 481)
      - Psalms Conferences (Lilly), 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 483)
    - Pending Searches
      - ISM/YSM Choral Search, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 485)
    - Correspondence/Miscellaneous, 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 486)
  - Divinity School
    - Facilities, 2001-2002 (Box 9, Folder 487)
    - Building Project (from authorization on), 2000-2001 (Box 9, Folder 489)